pennysaverusa.com 2009-09-25

# Free Online Classifieds in USA - find the best local values at PennySaverUSA.com - Privacy Policy

This policy governs the information activities of Harte Hanks Shoppers, Inc., Harte Hanks Flyer, Inc., The Flyer Publishing Corporation and their Web sites, TheFlyer.com and PennySaverUSA.com, including subdomains of these URLs, for example, newspapername.PennySaverUSA.com (collectively "PennySaverUSA" or "us" or "we") and not any other activity of Harte Hanks, Inc. or any of its affiliated companies. This policy discusses our information collection, use and sharing practices.

If you have any questions about this policy or our information handling practices, please contact us at [privacy@pennysaverusa.com](mailto:privacy@pennysaverusa.com?subject=Privacy+Policy).

  * **What Information About Individuals Do We Gather?**
  * **How Do We Use the Information That We Collect?**
  * **Do We Share Information We Receive?**
  * **How Secure Is Information About Me?**
  * **What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites?**
  * **What Information Can I Access?**
  * **What Choices Do I Have?**
  * **Are Children Allowed to Use Our Web Sites?**
  * **Do We Participate in the European Union Safe Harbor Program?**
  * **Conditions of Use, Policies, and Revisions**

* * *

## What Information About Individuals Do We Gather?

> **Personal Information** : Any personal information you give us, for example, by phone, credit card information, e-mail or postal mail, may be used, collected or stored by us or our service providers. For example, you may provide us with your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address, all of which we consider to be personal information. You can choose not to provide your personal information, but then you would not be able to take advantage of many of our services or place advertising with us.
> 
> **Nonpersonal Information** : We may receive, use and store certain types of nonpersonal information automatically whenever you interact with our Web site or online marketing, like our banner ads, or if you provide it to us upon request (like your zip code). For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," (click here for more about cookies) and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Web sites. Click here to see examples of the nonpersonal information we receive. We may also use clear gifs, which are also sometimes called Web bugs and 1x1 pixels, to monitor your interactions with our Web site or online marketing (such as, banners ads we place on other Web sites). The information that is collected in this process is the same information as with cookies. We may use persistent cookies to remember you when you come back for future visits. Such persistent cookies allow us to customize your visit, e.g., providing content directed to your ZIP Code if you had previously provided us with that ZIP Code.
> 
> For more information about the use of cookies and other similar technology, please visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). You may also visit that website to opt out from nonpersonal data collection from various third party, online advertising service providers. To delete cookies on your computer, you can select "delete cookies" within your Web browser.
> 
> **E-mail** : Generally, if you e-mail an advertiser in response to an ad you see on our Web site, the e-mail is processed by us, so we would have your e-mail by your submitting this e-mail. Additionally, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mails we send you or when you respond to something in an e-mail we send you to help us make these e-mails more useful and interesting to you.

We might obtain information about you from our sister companies and business partners and add it to information that you have previously provided to us in order to serve you better. Click here to see examples of the information we receive. We also compare our e-mail list to lists received from our sister companies and business partners, to try to avoid sending you unnecessary or duplicative messages.

* * *

## How Do We Use the Information That We Collect?

We use the personal information that you provide for various business purposes, such as placing and publishing your ads, processing requests or transactions, improving our publications and Web sites, contacting you regarding your advertising with us, conducting and fulfilling contests and sweepstakes, forwarding your requests to our advertisers, and communicating with you.

We use nonpersonal information to improve our Web site, your online user experience and online communications. We may combine nonpersonal information with your personal information, but in such a case, we will treat the information as a whole as personal information.

If you provide us with your e-mail or physical address, we may send you communications regarding your transactions with us (such as, the timing of when your ad ran), forward your communications to our advertisers if the communication relates to that advertiser, forward communications from our advertisers to you, or we may send you communications regarding items that might interest you, including content from our business partners or your potentially advertising with us.

Sometimes we send you offers that we believe may interest you on behalf of ourselves, our sister companies, our clients, our advertisers and other businesses.

* * *

## Do We Share Information It Receives?

Information about individuals is an important part of our business. We share your personal information as described below. Since nonpersonal information is not personal in nature, we may share it with third parties more generally.

> **Businesses Partners** : In some cases, our business partners provide offerings or listings, which could be provided in a co-branded or joint manner, such as with real estate and automobile listings. We share your personal information related to those transactions with that third party or that third party may collect information directly from you. If you request information regarding an offer or ad, we will provide your personal information to the respective business partner. Additionally, we may share personal information with our business partners so that our business partners may communicate with and provide offers to you.
> 
> **Third-Party Service Providers** : We employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf, including, hosting Web pages, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, serving online advertising and providing customer service. These providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes except on a nonpersonal basis. For example, information you provide to enter a contest or sweepstakes is provided to the vendor who is running the contest or sweepstakes.
> 
> **Sister Companies** : We may provide your personal information to our sister companies, that is those companies also owned directly or indirectly by Harte-Hanks, Inc., so that they can help correct or complete the information that we have about you and so that our sister companies can provide offers to you that may be of interest to you.
> 
> **Advertisers** : If you request information regarding an offer or ad, we will provide your personal information to that respective advertiser.

We may share nonpersonal information we gather to educate others about our services, to improve our services and for related business purposes.

If you include personal information in an advertisement you place with us, we will publish that personal information.

As our business develops over time, we may sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, confidential information generally is one of the transferred assets but remains subject to any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, you consent otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that we, or substantially all of our assets are acquired, confidential information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

We will transfer personal information when we believe the transfer is necessary to comply with the law; or to protect our rights or safety or the rights or safety of our users, our advertisers or others.

* * *

## How Secure Is Information About Me?

We take steps in accordance with industry practice to keep your personal information secure, such as training our employees to safeguard confidential information in our possession. Additionally, we maintain policies and procedures covering the proper logical and physical security of workplaces and records.  We require independent contractors and outside companies who work with us to adhere to privacy obligations through their contracts with us. We use technological means (such as backup files, virus detection and eradication software, firewalls, and other computer software and hardware) to protect against unauthorized access or alterations to personal information. For example, to the extent that we retain a customer’s credit card information, we encrypt that information while it resides on our servers.

We also work to protect the security of your financial information online during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you provide to us. SSL is the leading security protocol for data transfer on the Internet. This technology encrypts your account information as it moves between your PC's browser and our computer systems. When information is encrypted in this way, it becomes nearly impossible for anyone other than the credit card processing company to read it. This secure session helps protect the safety and confidentiality of your information.

Unfortunately, no data security methodology is 100% safe. Hence, it is just as important for you to protect yourself against unauthorized access to your information. You should be se sure to take such simple steps as signing off when finished using a shared computer, keeping your passwords in a secure location, and not sharing your passwords with any third parties.

* * *

## What About Web Site Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites?

Our Web sites includes third-party advertising, links to other Web sites and Web pages hosted by third party business partners. These third-party partners, Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They also may use cookies, JavaScript, clear gifs, and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their content and to personalize the content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers, their vendors and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We do require them by contract to take appropriate actions with regard to any personal data they may collect from you while you are on our Web site. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt out of their information collection.

* * *

## What Information Can I Access?

If you are one of our online advertisers or have an account on this Web site, you can access your name, address and phone number information online with us to view and update that information by logging in to our Web sites.

If you believe we have other personal information about you that you wish to access, please contact as noted in the paragraph below, but please note that if we do not have any personal information about you, we cannot tell you about any nonpersonal information that we might have about you.

* * *

## What Choices Do I Have?

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, please e-mail us at [privacy@pennysaverusa.com](mailto:privacy@pennysaverusa.com?subject=Privacy+Policy).

If you do not want to receive our print publications or telephone calls from us, call us toll free at (800) 422-4116 for California and South Florida or (813) 626-SELL for West Florida or write to us at:

> **FOR CALIFORNIA & SOUTH FLORIDA**: 
> 
> Harte-Hanks Shoppers  
> Attn: Consumer Preferences  
> 2830 Orbiter Street  
> Brea, CA 92821
> 
> **FOR WEST FLORIDA** : 
> 
> Circulation  
> The Flyer  
> 201 Kelsey Lane  
> Tampa, FL 33619

However, we will continue to contact you as necessary to process any transactions.

* * *

## Are Children Allowed to Use Our Web Site?

Our Web sites are not intended for children, although children's products are offered for sale to be purchased by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our Web sites only with the permission of a parent or guardian.

* * *

## Do We Participate in the European Safe Harbor Program?

Since we collects and processes personal information in the United States, we are a participant through our parent company, Harte Hanks, Inc., in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view the certification of Harte-Hanks, visit the [U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/) Web site.

If you believe that we are not in compliance with the Safe Harbor principles, first contact our company by mail, e-mail, or telephone as noted in this policy. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you can then contact the DMA Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution Program. The DMA will then serve as a liaison to us to resolve your concerns. You can reach the DMA Safe Harbor Program at:

> Safe Harbor Line  
> Direct Marketing Association  
> 1111 19th Street, NW - Suite 1100  
> Washington, DC 20036-3603
> 
> Tel. (202) 861-2445

* * *

## Conditions of Use, Policies, and Revisions

If you choose to visit our Web sites or advertise with us, your online visit and advertising is subject to our Policy which is available at the top of this page. If you have any concern about our privacy practices, please [contact us](mailto:privacy@pennysaverusa.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).

Our business is continuously evolving, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions also may change. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

* * *

## More Information:

**Cookies**

Cookies are alphanumeric text files that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to, personalized your visit based on such items as your ZIP Code and prior page views.

Most browsers will provide you with information on how to prevent the browser from accepting new cookies, how to delete your cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether, although, we recommend that you leave them turned on to receive the full functionality of our Web site and the Internet in general.

**Nonpersonal Information**

Examples of the nonpersonal information we collect and analyze on an automated basis include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; machine access code (MAC), cookie number; pages and ads you viewed or searched for. During some visits we may use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

**Information from Other Sources**

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from third parties, which we use to correct our records and; page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links from Google) and data that we might obtain from our sister companies to confirm or correct information provided by you or to provide us a more complete picture of who you are.

**Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Web sites**

Examples of third-party advertisers and advertising companies that you can link to from this Web site or that serve advertising content directly to your browser on certain of our web pages include [247 Media](http://www.247media.com/), [MaxOnline](http://www.maxonline.com/), [Google](http://www.google.com/), [Mediaplex](http://www.mediaplex.com/), [Atlas](http://www.atlassolutions.com/) and [Doubleclick](http://www.doubleclick.com/). You can find out more about their information collection and use practices, including how to opt out of cookies and other collection techniques that they use, by clicking on the above links to their Web sites.
